/*const Question(
      question: "Which datatype hold the both value of int and double?",
      options: ["numeric", "int", "double", "num"],
      answerIndex: 3,
    ),
    const Question(
      question: "....... data type can be used to represent true or false",
      options: ["numeric", "int", "bool", "boolean"],
      answerIndex: 2,
    ),
    const Question(
      question: "Which of the following is not arithematic operator?",
      options: ["#", "/", "+", "-"],
      answerIndex: 0,
    ),
    const Question(
      question: "....... property is used to check the runtime data",
      options: ["runtimeType", "typeOf", "instanceOf", "runtime"],
      answerIndex: 0,
    ),
    const Question(
      question: "Which data type used to declare string",
      options: ["char", "string", "String", "str"],
      answerIndex: 2,
    ),
  ];*/

  /*{
      "question": "Which datatype hold the both value of int and double?",
      "option": ["numeric", "int", "double", "num"],
      "answerIndex": 3,
    },
    {
      "question": "....... data type can be used to represent true or false",
      "option": ["numeric", "int", "bool", "boolean"],
      "answerIndex": 2,
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not arithematic operator?",
      "option": ["#", "/", "+", "-"],
      "answerIndex": 0,
    },
    {
      "question": "....... property is used to check the runtime data",
      "option": ["runtimeType", "typeOf", "instanceOf", "runtime"],
      "answerIndex": 0,
    },
    {
      "question": "Which data type used to declare string",
      "option": ["char", "string", "String", "str"],
      "answerIndex": 2,
    }*/